{
    "Q1" : {
        "type":"pick",
        "question":"Who is the creator of WeekGolf?",
        "answers": ["Lynn", "Lyndon", "TKirishima", "ShaneTheGamer", "Lyxal", "JoKing", "Pardouin", "Steffan"],
        "correct": "TKirishima",
        "proba": 1
    },

    "Q2" : {
        "type":"pick",
        "question":"How many programming languages are there on WeekGolf?",
        "answers": ["-1", "31", "16", "25", "27", "29", "21", "28"],
        "correct": "28",
        "proba": 1
    },

    "Q3" : {
        "type":"pick",
        "question":"When did WeekGolf become public?",
        "answers": ["1st July 2022", "1st June 2022", "1st July 2021", "1st Aug 2022", "1 may 2022", "1st June 2021", "1st Aug 2021"],
        "correct": "1st July 2022",
        "proba": 1
    },

    "Q4" : {
        "type":"pick",
        "question":"What was the first problem on WeekGolf?",
        "answers": ["Fibonacci&Binary", "Ulam Of Ulam", "Nearest Alpha", "Palindromic Range", "New Alphabet", "#RGB", "Collatz Mean"],
        "correct": "Fibonacci&Binary",
        "proba": 1
    },

    "Q5" : {
        "type":"pick",
        "question":"Generally, which language is the shortest between Rust, Go, Java and C#?",
        "answers": ["Go", "Java", "C#", "Rust"],
        "correct": "C#",
        "proba": 1
    },

    "Q6" : {
        "type":"pick",
        "question":"Generally, which language is the shortest between APL, K, J and Julia?",
        "answers": ["APL", "K", "J", "Julia"],
        "correct": "APL",
        "proba": 1
    },

    "Q7" : {
        "type":"pick",
        "question":"Generally, which language is the shortest between Python, Ruby, JavaScript and Bash?",
        "answers": ["Ruby", "JavaScript", "Bash", "Python"],
        "correct": "Ruby",
        "proba": 1
    },

    "Q8" : {
        "type":"pick",
        "question":"Generally, which language is the shortest between Raku, Ruby, Perl and Bash?",
        "answers": ["Ruby", "Raku", "Bash", "Perl"],
        "correct": "Raku",
        "proba": 1
    },

    "Q9" : {
        "type":"pick",
        "question":"How many single character languages are there on WeekGolf?",
        "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4","5","6","7","8","9","yes"],
        "correct": "4",
        "proba": 1
    },

    "Q10" : {
        "type":"pick",
        "question":"Who is the user with the most points on WeekGolf?",
        "answers": ["TKirishima", "Lyndon", "Steffan", "ShaneTheGamer","JoKing","Lynn","Natanael","Pardouin"," AlephSquirrel"],
        "correct": "Steffan",
        "proba": 1
    },

    "Q11" : {
        "type":"pick",
        "question":"What is the first language added thanks to the votes?",
        "answers": ["Vyxal", "J", "GolfScript", "Jelly","APL","Prolog"],
        "correct": "Vyxal",
        "proba": 1
    },

    "Q12" : {
        "type":"pick",
        "question":"In WeekGolf, what is the letter with which the most languages begin?",
        "answers": ["R", "J", "P", "C","K"],
        "correct": "J",
        "proba": 1
    },

    "Q13" : {
        "type": "set",
        "question": "In which year was <PARAM> officially created?",
        "answers": {
            "APL": "1966",
            "Bash": "1989",
            "C": "1972",
            "C++": "1985",
            "C#": "2002",
            "Clojure": "2007",
            "Elixir": "2011",
            "Go": "2009",
            "Golfscript": "2007",
            "Haskell": "1990",
            "J": "1990",
            "Java": "1995",
            "JavaScript": "1995",
            "Jelly": "2015",
            "K": "1993",
            "Kotlin": "2011",
            "Lua": "1993",
            "OCaml": "1996",
            "Perl": "1987",
            "PHP": "1994",
            "Prolog": "1972",
            "Python": "1991",
            "R": "1993",
            "Raku": "2015",
            "Ruby": "1995",
            "Rust": "2006",
            "Vyxal": "2020"
        },
        "proba": 5
    },

    "Q14" : {
        "type": "set",
        "question": "In which language is the program correct:",
        "description": "<PARAM>",
        "answers": {
            "```\na ← 0\nb ← 1\nNext ← {\n\tsum ← +/ ⍵\n\tsum , ⎕ ← ⊃ ⍵\n}\nNext ⍣ 10 ⊢ a b```": "APL",
            "```bash\na=0\nb=1\n\nfor ((i=0; i<10; i++)); do\n\techo $a\n\ta=$((b-a))\n\tb=$((b+a))\ndone```": "Bash",
            "```c\n#include <stdio.h>\n\nint main (void) {\n\tint a = 0, b = 1;\n\n\tfor (int i = 0; i < 10; i++){\n\t\tprintf(\"%d\\n\", a);\n\t\ta = b - a;\n\t\tb += a;\n\t}\n\n\treturn 0;\n}```": "C",
            "```cpp\n#include <iostream>\n\nint main() {\n\tint a = 0, b = 1;\n\n\tfor (int i = 0; i < 10; i++){\n\t\tstd::cout << a << std::endl;\n\t\ta = b - a;\n\t\tb += a;\n\t}\n}```": "C++",
            "```cs\n// Only works for C#10 and +\nint a = 0, b = 1;\n\nfor (int i = 0; i < 10; i++){\n\tConsole.WriteLine(a);\n\t(a, b) = (b, a + b);\n}```": "C#",
            "```clj\n(def fib-seq-seq\n((fn fib [a b] \n\t(lazy-seq (cons a (fib b (+ a b)))))\n0 1))\n\n(println (clojure.string/join \"\n\" (take 10 fib-seq-seq)))```": "Clojure",
            "```erl\ndefmodule Fib do \n\tdef fib(0) do 0 end\n\tdef fib(1) do 1 end\n\tdef fib(n) do fib(n-1) + fib(n-2) end\nend\n\nfor i <- 0..9 do\n\tIO.puts Fib.fib(i)\nend```": "Elixir",
            "```go\npackage main\n\nimport \"fmt\"\n\nfunc main() {\n\ta, b := 0, 1\n\t\n\tfor i := 0; i < 10; i++ {\n\t\tfmt.Println(a)\n\t\ta = b - a\n\t\tb += a\n\t}\n}```": "Go",
            "```\n0 :a ;\n1 :b ;\n10 ,\n{;\n\ta puts\n\tb   a b + :b ;   :a;\n}\n/\n\nexit;```": "GolfScript",
            "```hs\nfib :: Int -> Int -> Int -> IO()\nfib a b 0 = print a\nfib a b n = do\n\tprint a \n\tfib b (a+b) (n-1)\n\t\nmain = do\n\tfib 0 1 9```": "Haskell",
            "```\nfibN =: (-&2 +&$: -&1)^:(1&<) M.\"0\necho fibN  i.10\nexit ''```": "J",
            "```java\nclass prog {\n\tpublic static void main(String[] args) {\n\t\tint a = 0, b = 1;\n\n\t\tfor (int i = 0; i < 10; i++){\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(a);\n\t\t\ta = b - a;\n\t\t\tb += a;\n\t\t}\n\t}\n}```": "Java",
            "```\nlet a = 0, b = 1;\n\nfor (let i = 0; i < 10; i++) {\n\tconsole.log(a);\n\t[a, b] = [b, a+b]\n}```": "JavaScript",
            "```\n+9Ð¡1\n\t   - No input, so left argument (value of a) implicitly zero\n9Ð¡\t- Apply 9 times, where a=0 and...\n\t1  - The right argument (b) = 1\n+\t  - Addition```": "Jelly",
            "```py\nlet a=0;b=1\n\tfor i=0:9\n\t\tprintln(a)\n\t\ta,b=b,a+b\n\tend\nend```": "Julia",
            "```\nl: 0 1\n{l::l, +/-2#l}'!8;\n`0: \"\n\" / $l```": "K",
            "```kt\nfun main() {\n\tvar a = 0\n\tvar b = 1\n\n\trepeat(10) {\n\t\tprintln(a)\n\t\tb += a\n\t\ta = b - a\n\t}\n}```": "Kotlin",
            "```lua\na=0 \nb=1\nfor _ = 1,10 do\n\tprint(a)\n\ta,b=b,a+b\nend```": "Lua",
            "```ml\nlet rec fib a b n =\n\tPrintf.printf \"%d\n\" a;\n\tif n > 0 then fib b (a+b) (n-1);;\n\nfib 0 1 9;;```": "OCaml",
            "```pl\n$a = 0;\n$b = 1;\nfor ($i = 0; $i < 10; $i++) {\n\tprint \"$a\n\";\n\t($a, $b) = ($b, $a + $b);\n}```": "Perl",
            "```php\n<?php\n$a = 0;\n$b = 1;\nfor ($i = 0; $i < 10; $i++) {\n\techo \"$a\n\";\n\t[$a, $b] = [$b, $a + $b];\n}```": "PHP",
            "```\nmain :-\n\tf(0,1,12).\n\nf(I,J,N) :-\n\tK is J,\n\tL is I+J,\n\tM is N-1,\n\tM>0,\n\twriteln(I),\n\tf(K, L, M).```": "Prolog",
            "```py\na = 0\nb = 1\nfor i in range(10):\n\tprint(a)\n\ta, b = b, a+b```": "Python",
            "```r\na=0\nb=1\nfor(i in 1:10){\n\tcat(b<-(a=a+b)-b)\n\tcat(\"\n\")\n}```": "R",
            "```pl\nmy $a = 0;\nmy $b = 1;\nfor 0..9 {\n\tsay $a;\n\t($a, $b) = ($b, $a + $b);\n}```": "Raku",
            "```rb\na = 0\nb = 1\n10.times do\n\tp a\n\ta, b = b, a+b\nend```": "Ruby",
            "```rs\nfn main() {\n\tlet mut a = 0;\n\tlet mut b = 1;\n\t\n\tfor i in 0..10 {\n\t\tprintln!(\"{}\", a);\n\t\ta = b - a;\n\t\tb += a;\n\t}\n}```": "Rust",
            "```\n0 →a\n1 →b\n10 (\n\t←a ,\n\t←a ←b ~+ →b →a \n\t_ # Remove the value of a left by ~+\n)```": "Vyxal"
        },
        "proba": 5
    },

    "Q15" : {
        "type": "set",
        "question": "To which problem does this input belong?",
        "description": "<PARAM>",
        "answers": {
            "RBT\nXO\n-O": "Candies for Halloween",
            "1\n5\n9": "Basic sequence",
            "27.5": "Music Notes",
            "RNBQKBNR\nPPPPPPPP\n # # # #\n# # # # \n # # # #\n# # # # \npppppppp\nrnbqkbnr": "Chess Points",
            "Steve Alex\n1 100 2\n3 2 3": "American Presidents",
            "#012345": "#RGB",
            "ZYXWVUTSRQPONMLKJIHGFEDCBA\nREVERSE\nIVEVIHV": "New Alphabet",
            "Hello world!": "Fibonacci&Binary"
        },
        "proba": 3
    },

    "Q16" : {
        "type": "set",
        "question": "To which problem does this output belong?",
        "description": "<PARAM>",
        "answers": {
            "PrimeFibo\n6\nPrime\nFibo": "Prime, Fibo, Fizz",
            "C#6": "Music Notes",
            "+6": "Chess Points",
            "Steve won": "American Presidents",
            "R": "#RGB",
            "1\n1 1\n1 3 1": "Tribonacci Triangle",
            "IVEVIHV\nREVERSE": "New Alphabet",
            "0\n46\n46\n92\n138\n230\n...": "Fibonacci&Binary"
        },
        "proba": 3
    },

    "Q17" : {
        "type": "pick",
        "question": "Which of these languages require a dollar sign before the name of a variable?",
        "answers": ["Perl", "Python", "GolfScript", "Vyxal", "APL", "Prolog", "JavaScript", "The USA?"],
        "correct": "Perl",
        "proba": 1
    },

    "Q18" : {
        "type": "pick",
        "question": "Which language isn't in WeekGolf?",
        "answers": ["Scala", "Prolog", "APL", "Bash", "Elixir", "Jelly", "Clojure"],
        "correct": "Scala",
        "proba": 1
    },

    "Q19" : {
        "type": "pick",
        "question": "Which language is in WeekGolf?",
        "answers": ["Scala", "Swift", "BQN", "Zsh", "Visual Basic", "J", "Husk", "Brainfuck"],
        "correct": "J",
        "proba": 1
    },

    "Q20" : {
        "type": "set",
        "question": "What problem does this program solve?",
        "description": "<PARAM>",
        "answers": {
            "```\n`0:$+\\[14;0;+//2\\0:0]```": "Fibonacci & Binary",
            "```clj\n(pr(nth(iterate(reduce(fn[u x](if(=(count(filter #(and(not=(* 2 %)x)(.contains u(- x %)))u))2)(conj u x)u))[0 1 2](range 3 801))(read))(read)))```": "Ulam of Ulam",
            "```ml\nlet rec x=read_int()and f x=x>0&(x mod 16<10||f(x/16))and g i=f(x+i)&f(x-i)&g(i+1)||()=print_int i;;g 0```": "Nearest Alpha",
            "```\nS⌈⌊ʀ⟑R=∑C₴ # Abvious one btw```": "Palindromic Range",
            "```bash\nread s\ntr A-Z $s```": "New Alphabet",
            "```lua\na,n=io.read():match\"(.+) (.+)\"x={a}y={a,a}for i=1,n do print(table.concat(x,\" \"))z={a}for j=1,i do z[j+1]=y[j]+x[j]+y[j+1]end z[i+2]=a x=y y=z end```": "Tribonacci Triangle",
            "```hs\nv x|all(>\"f\")x=\"1\"|1<2=[snd$maximum$zip(\"1\":x)\"0RGB\"]\ng(#)x=v[1#x,3#x,5#x]\nmain=interact$g drop```": "#RGB",
            "```prolog\nN+M:-get0(C),C>10,N*10-C+48+M;N>1,F is N/\\1,N*3/(6-5*F)+F+T,N<T,M=T;M=N.\nN-I-J-S:-N> -J,format(\"~d\n\",S//(N+I));N+M,N+1-I-J-(S+M).\nmain:-0+I,0+J,-I-I-J-0.```": "Collatz Mean",
            "```\n⎕←' won',⍨⊃({1>+/(2⊃⊢/×∘×-\\)∘⍎¨1↓⍵}↓' '(≠⊆⊢)⊃)⎕sh'dd'```": "American Presidents",
            "```rs\nuse std::io::*;fn main(){print!(\"{:+}\",stdin().bytes().fold(0,|n,t|(|c|n+1941%(c&19^4)*(255/c%3-1))(t.unwrap()as i16)))}```": "Chess Points",
            "```pl\nprint+(map<$_ $_#>,A..G)[(($==17.31234*log<>/15.886)%12+4)/.9%14],$=/=12```": "Music notes",
            "```pl\nsay \"Prime\"x.is-prime~\"Fibo\"x($_∈(0,1,*+*...*>$_))||$_ for +get..get```": "Prime, Fibo, Fizz",
            "```js\nfor(b=(P=prompt)(a=P(t=0)-1);a++<b;t+=P<s,t-=P>s,P=s)for(s=i=a;i--;)s+=a%i?0:i\nconsole.log(t)```": "Divisors comparison",
            "```php\n<?for($n=`dd`;$n-$m=strrev($n);++$i)$n+=$m;echo+$i;```": "Not Lychrel",
            "```rb\nr,s=*$<\nf=->{eval s.chars*\"%s\"%(_1.chars*9)}\n$><<('0\n'..r).map{[f['*+'],s,s=\"#{f[?+]+f[?*]}\"]}.max[1]```": "Double Persistence",
            "```\nƓ;Ɠ;ƓU_I$×÷/2Ƥ$IE$?Ḣ;Ɗ9¡µS^µṀ_Ṃ```": "Basic Sequence"
        },
        "proba": 5
    }
}
